♪I've braved the storms, walked through the rain♪
♪ لقد تحدت العواصف ، مشيت عبر المطر ♪
♪Seen the highs and lows along the way♪
♪ شاهد الارتفاعات والانخفاض على طول الطريق ♪
♪But you stay quiet, never change♪
♪ لكنك تبقى هادئًا ، ولا تتغير أبدًا ♪
♪Like a child who dreams beneath the stars♪
♪ مثل الطفل الذي يحلم تحت النجوم ♪
♪I've read the story in your eyes♪
♪ لقد قرأت القصة في عينيك ♪
♪And finally, nothing's left to hide♪
♪ وأخيرا ، لم يتبق شيء للاختباء ♪
♪You won't give in to a world so cold♪
♪ لن تستسلم لعالم بارد جدًا ♪
♪So you wander through it on your own♪
♪ لذا تتجول من خلالها بمفردك ♪
♪Maybe fate has drawn us near♪
♪ ربما جذبنا المصير بالقرب من ♪
♪Just to help you learn to believe♪
♪ فقط لمساعدتك في تعلم التصديق ♪
♪Everything you've questioned deep inside♪
♪ كل ما شكك في عمقه ♪
♪I'll be the proof you need♪
♪ سأكون الدليل الذي تحتاجه ♪
♪I've made my choice♪
♪ لقد اخترت اختياري ♪
♪For you, I'll be brave and break the rules♪
♪ بالنسبة لك ، سأكون شجاعًا وكسر القواعد ♪
♪What's there to fear even if the world is right and I am wrong?♪
♪ ما الذي يخشىه حتى لو كان العالم على حق وأنا مخطئ؟ ♪
♪One day, all of this will turn into memories♪
♪ في يوم من الأيام ، كل هذا سيتحول إلى ذكريات ♪
♪Every storm we faced will turn into our life's scenery♪
♪ كل عاصفة واجهناها ستتحول إلى مشهد حياتنا ♪
♪For you, I'll be brave and break the rules♪
♪ بالنسبة لك ، سأكون شجاعًا وكسر القواعد ♪
♪What's there to fear even if the world is right and I am wrong?♪
♪ ما الذي يخشىه حتى لو كان العالم على حق وأنا مخطئ؟ ♪
♪Even if, in the end, the whole world turns against me♪
♪ حتى لو كان العالم كله في النهاية يتحول ضدي ♪
♪I won't regret having loved you♪
♪ لن أندم على أنني أحببتك ♪
♪With all my heart♪
♪ من كل قلبي ♪
♪I've held you close♪
♪ لقد حملتك على مقربة ♪
♪Walked by your side♪
♪ سار بجانبك ♪
♪And loved the fire that burned inside you♪
♪ وأحب النار التي أحرقت بداخلك ♪
[The First Frost]
[الصقيع الأول]
[Adapted from the novel of the same name by Zhu Yi on www.jjwxc.net]
[مقتبس من رواية نفس الاسم بواسطة Zhu Yi على www.jjwxc.net]
Hello.
مرحبًا.
I'd like to book a room.
أود حجز غرفة.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
All guests must register.
يجب على جميع الضيوف التسجيل.
I'm not staying.
أنا لا أقيم.
There's one more room next door. Want it?
هناك غرفة أخرى مجاورة. تريده؟
I'm just walking her up.
أنا فقط أسير لها.
This is just the usual trick
هذه مجرد الحيلة المعتادة
of you young guys these days.
منكم الشباب هذه الأيام.
Rules state
حالة القواعد
you must register.
يجب عليك التسجيل.
I can go up myself.
أستطيع أن أصعد بنفسي.
Then remember to lock your door tonight.
ثم تذكر قفل بابك الليلة.
Are you still practicing tonight?
هل ما زلت تمارس الليلة؟
I'll probably go over a few moves.
ربما سأذهب إلى بعض التحركات.
Don't stress. You got this.
لا تشدد. لقد حصلت على هذا.
You're not the examiner.
أنت لست الفاحص.
How do you know?
كيف علمت بذلك؟
I know a bit about the arts.
أنا أعرف قليلا عن الفنون.
- I think your dancing is... - Hello.
- أعتقد أن رقصك هو ... - مرحبًا.
Room 306.
غرفة 306.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I'm going up now.
أنا ذاهب الآن.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Are you sure you don't want the room?
هل أنت متأكد أنك لا تريد الغرفة؟
No need.
لا حاجة.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
To get a room.
للحصول على غرفة.
We're fully booked.
نحن محجوزون بالكامل.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Front desk staff.
طاقم مكتب الاستقبال.
I'll pay extra.
سأدفع إضافية.
Even with extra, we're still full.
حتى مع الإضافية ، ما زلنا ممتلئين.
See? The lights are off.
يرى؟ الأنوار متطفلة.
Sorry.
آسف.
Try checking ahead.
حاول التحقق إلى الأمام.
[To Wen Shuangjiang: Just picture the examiners as pumpkins.]
[إلى Wen Shuangjiang: فقط تصور الفاحصين على أنهم القرع.]
Next up, scene performance.
المقبل ، أداء المشهد.
Candidate No. 7, Wen Yifan,
المرشح رقم 7 ، وين ييفان ،
please get ready.
يرجى الاستعداد.
♪My heart races, and even my breath pauses♪
♪ سباقات قلبي ، وحتى أنفاسي يتوقف ♪
♪I can't control myself♪
♪ لا يمكنني التحكم في نفسي ♪
♪My mind is full of you♪
♪ عقلي مليء بك ♪
♪Stubborn and restless, every step is hard♪
♪ عنيد ومريح ، كل خطوة صعبة ♪
♪I've always been cautious♪
لقد كنت دائمًا حذرًا ♪
♪But now I want to tell you♪
♪ ولكن الآن أريد أن أخبرك ♪
♪I like you very much♪
♪ أنا معجب بك كثيرا ♪
♪Like spring blossoms lasting into summer nights...♪
♪ مثل أزهار الربيع التي تستمر في ليالي الصيف ... ♪
It's been a while
لقد مر وقت
since you were this happy, right?
منذ أن كنت سعيدا ، أليس كذلك؟
♪Like tears falling into the sea, escaping loneliness♪
♪ مثل الدموع التي تسقط في البحر ، هربًا من الوحدة ♪
♪I simply like you, without caring about the ending♪
♪ أنا ببساطة أحبك ، دون الاهتمام بالنهاية ♪
[Episode 12] [How to Be Happy?]
[الحلقة 12] [كيف تكون سعيدا؟]
[3143 Days]
[3143 يومًا]
I'm living happily now.
أنا أعيش بسعادة الآن.
I have my own family.
لدي عائلتي.
Please,
لو سمحت،
stop looking for me.
توقف عن البحث عني.
Auntie,
العمة ،
if she doesn't want to see you,
إذا كانت لا تريد رؤيتك ،
please don't look for her.
من فضلك لا تبحث عنها.
Yuqing asked me
سألني Yuqing
to give this to you.
لإعطاء هذا لك.
This is ransom money
هذا هو المال الفدية
to buy back her freedom?
لتراجع حريتها؟
She hopes
إنها تأمل
you'll start a new life too.
ستبدأ حياة جديدة أيضًا.
Please, just let her go.
من فضلك ، فقط دعها تذهب.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
Yifan.
ييفان.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Need my help with something?
هل تحتاج إلى مساعدتي في شيء ما؟
No.
لا.
Okay.
تمام.
Yifan.
ييفان.
After you finish editing,
بعد الانتهاء من التحرير ،
will you come to my welcome party?
هل ستأتي إلى حفلة الترحيب الخاصة بي؟
Not sure.
لست متأكدا.
I'll see how things go.
سأرى كيف تسير الأمور.
But I really hope you will.
لكنني حقا أتمنى أن تفعل.
Yifan,
ييفان ،
Still working? Everyone's left.
ما زلت تعمل؟ غادر الجميع.
Yeah, Yifan.
نعم ، ييفان.
You have to come
عليك أن تأتي
to our welcome party!
في حفلة الترحيب لدينا!
Please!
لو سمحت!
Come on.
تعال.
Su Tian is already there.
سو تيان موجود بالفعل.
We're just waiting for you.
نحن فقط في انتظارك.
Join us!
انضم إلينا!
Alright, I'll try once I'm done.
حسنًا ، سأحاول بمجرد انتهائي.
Okay?
تمام؟
Okay, we'll wait for you.
حسنًا ، سننتظر لك.
- Let's go! Mu Chengyun, hurry! - See you there.
- دعنا نذهب! مو تشينجيون ، عجل! - أراك هناك.
So,
لذا،
see you tonight.
نراكم الليلة.
Look at you.
انظر إليك.
Still thinking about sleep?
ما زلت أفكر في النوم؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Remember everything I said.
تذكر كل ما قلته.
Yifan.
ييفان.
Mr. Gan.
السيد غان.
You're still here?
هل ما زلت هنا؟
I just finished a meeting with them.
لقد انتهيت للتو من اجتماع معهم.
Come on. Let's go join the party.
تعال. دعنا نذهب للانضمام إلى الحفلة.
I'm skipping.
أنا أتخطى.
I'm heading home first.
أنا أتجه إلى المنزل أولاً.
Bye.
الوداع.
Yifan.
ييفان.
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
This place
هذا المكان
isn't like Yihe Daily, right?
ليس مثل ياهي يوميا ، أليس كذلك؟
If anyone
إذا كان أي شخص
harasses you in any way,
يضايقك بأي شكل من الأشكال ،
you have to tell me.
عليك أن تخبرني.
I won't let them get away with it.
لن أدعهم يفلتون من ذلك.
No one has.
لا أحد لديه.
Good.
جيد.
I was just worried.
كنت قلقة فقط.
You never join gatherings.
أنت لا تنضم أبدًا للتجمعات.
Is there another reason?
هل هناك سبب آخر؟
Really no.
حقا لا.
Our colleagues here
زملائنا هنا
are pretty easygoing, right?
هل هي سهلة جدا ، أليس كذلك؟
Everyone's nice.
الجميع لطيف.
So what's stopping you?
إذن ما الذي يمنعك؟
Alright, go grab your bag.
حسنا ، اذهب للاستيلاء على حقيبتك.
I'll go get the car.
سأذهب للحصول على السيارة.
Mr. Gan...
السيد غان ...
[Overtime]
[متأخر , بعد فوات الوقت]
Hello, we have a reservation.
مرحبا ، لدينا حجز.
Miss Wen!
ملكة جمال ون!
Your friends are upstairs.
أصدقاؤك في الطابق العلوي.
I'll take you to them.
سآخذك إليهم.
You've been here before?
هل كنت هنا من قبل؟
This way.
من هنا.
Just head up, and you'll see them.
فقط توجه ، وستراهم.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Enjoying yourself?
تتمتع بنفسك؟
Mr. Gan!
السيد غان!
The boss is here!
الرئيس هنا!
Yifan.
ييفان.
Take a seat!
شغل مقعد!
Yifan, sit here.
ييفان ، اجلس هنا.
- Thanks. - Let me get your bag.
- شكرًا. - دعني أحصل على حقيبتك.
No need. I can handle it.
لا حاجة. يمكنني التعامل معها.
It's fine. Leave it there.
لا بأس. اتركها هناك.
- So... - Thanks.
- لذلك ... - شكرا.
Everyone,
الجميع،
tonight,
الليلة،
we're here mainly
نحن هنا بشكل رئيسي
to welcome our two new colleagues.
للترحيب زملائنا الجدد.
You two
أنتما
don't need to be nervous.
لا تحتاج إلى أن تكون عصبيًا.
Just treat this workplace like home.
مجرد التعامل مع مكان العمل هذا مثل المنزل.
Also,
أيضًا،
everyone's been working hard.
الجميع يعمل بجد.
Tonight,
الليلة،
drink up
اشرب
and eat up!
وتناول الطعام!
It's on me!
إنه على عاتقي!
That's what we've been waiting for!
هذا ما كنا ننتظره!
Cheers!
هتافات!
Cheers, everyone!
هتافات ، الجميع!
Come on!
تعال!
- Let's go! - Thanks.
- دعنا نذهب! - شكرًا.
Boss.
رئيس.
Why bother coming over?
لماذا تهتم بالمجيء؟
You worked all day already.
لقد عملت طوال اليوم بالفعل.
We got this.
لقد حصلنا على هذا.
No need for you to worry.
لا حاجة لك للقلق.
Not welcome me?
لا نرحب بي؟
Boss, what do you want to drink?
بوس ، ماذا تريد أن تشرب؟
I'll mix one for you.
سأخلط واحد من أجلك.
No drinking. I'm driving.
لا شرب. أنا أقود.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
your friends are holding a party upstairs.
أصدقاؤك يحملون حفلة في الطابق العلوي.
Glad you came.
سعيد لأنك جئت.
May I
ربما أنا
stand on your left?
الوقوف على يسارك؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Because this way,
لأن بهذه الطريقة ،
I'll be closer to your heart.
سأكون أقرب إلى قلبك.
Just think of it as a reward
فقط فكر في الأمر كمكافأة
for my hard work these days.
لعملي الشاق هذه الأيام.
Yifan.
ييفان.
Where's that classmate of yours?
أين زميلك في الفصل الخاص بك؟
We didn't see him today.
لم نراه اليوم.
Who?
من؟
The one who's...
من هو ...
handsome and miserable.
وسيم وبائسة.
Who?
من؟
Here.
هنا.
Check out my idol.
تحقق من بلدي المعبود.
Look at him.
انظر إليه.
Who stays this calm in a fire?
من يبقى هذا الهدوء في النار؟
[This side profile is amazing!] Happy, I am very happy...
[هذا الملف الجانبي مذهل!] سعيد ، أنا سعيد جدا ...
Isn't that Senior Sang Yan?
أليست هذا كبار الغناء يان؟
Senior?
كبير؟
He's from our school, too?
إنه من مدرستنا أيضًا؟
Yeah.
نعم.
He was in the same class as another senior I'm close with.
لقد كان في نفس الفصل مثل آخر من كبار أنا على مقربة منه.
So, back then,
لذلك ، في ذلك الوقت ،
I tagged along
أنا وضع علامة على طول
to their graduation dinner.
لعشاء التخرج.
After the dinner,
بعد العشاء ،
did anything crazy happen?
هل حدث أي شيء مجنون؟
Not really.
ليس حقيقيًا.
But I do remember one thing.
لكني أتذكر شيئًا واحدًا.
At the graduation dinner,
في عشاء التخرج ،
most people
معظم الناس
had a few drinks,
تناول بعض المشروبات ،
except for two,
باستثناء اثنين ،
the legends of the Computer Science department,
أساطير قسم علوم الكمبيوتر ،
Sang Yan and Duan Jiaxu.
سانج يان و دوان جياكو.
One didn't touch a drop,
لم يلمس المرء قطرة ،
the other downed bottles like water,
الزجاجات الأخرى التي سقطت مثل المياه ،
over ten bottles.
أكثر من عشر زجاجات.
Ten bottles?
عشر زجاجات؟
Who drank them?
من شربهم؟
Sang Yan.
غنى يان.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I'm just a little unsteady.
أنا فقط غير مستقر قليلاً.
Unsteady, huh?
غير مستقر ، هاه؟
Let go.
اتركه.
I'm talking to you.
أنا أتحدث معك.
Senior Sang Yan.
غنى كبار يان.
Who's your senior?
من هو كبير لك؟
I'm a Nanwu University student, too, you know.
أنا طالب جامعة نانو ، كما تعلمون.
Could you be a little nicer to me?
هل يمكن أن تكون أجمل قليلا بالنسبة لي؟
Wen Yifan.
وين ييفان.
Can you stand still?
هل يمكنك الوقوف صامدًا؟
Then do me a favor.
ثم اعمل لي معروفًا.
Open the car door.
افتح باب السيارة.
Need help?
هل تحتاج إلى مساعدة؟
Yeah.
نعم.
No.
لا.
You're clumsy
أنت خرقاء
and careless.
وإهمال.
You can't take care
لا يمكنك العناية
of my frail junior!
من صغار الضعف!
Yifan,
ييفان ،
get in and sit next to me...
الدخول والجلوس بجواري ...
I'm heading out.
أنا أتجه.
Take the front seat.
خذ المقعد الأمامي.
Hurry up.
عجل.
Mind our foot.
ضع في اعتبارك قدمنا.
Where do you live?
أين تعيش؟
Nanwu University.
جامعة نانو.
- We're here. - Wait in the car.
- نحن هنا. - انتظر في السيارة.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Get up.
استيقظ.
Senior Sang Yan,
غنى كبار ،
I can walk on my own.
يمكنني المشي بمفردي.
You're awake?
أنت مستيقظ؟
Aren't you an actor?
ألست فاعلًا؟
That was terrible acting.
كان هذا التمثيل الرهيب.
What?
ماذا؟
I pulled
لقد سحبت
that little trick ages ago.
تلك الخدعة الصغيرة منذ العصور.
And you think it's your turn now?
وأنت تعتقد أن دورك الآن؟
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
For me to carry you in?
بالنسبة لي لأحملك؟
Stay safe.
ابق آمنًا.
Is he feeling better?
هل يشعر بتحسن؟
He's faking it. Can't you tell?
إنه مزيفها. لا يمكنك أن تقول؟
You're leaving, too?
أنت تغادر أيضًا؟
The teacher
المعلم
finally treated you guys to dinner.
تعاملت أخيرًا يا رفاق على العشاء.
Didn't Su Hao'an say
لم يقل سو هاوان
you were going on a night tour?
كنت ذاهب في جولة ليلية؟
I'm not interested.
أنا لست مهتم
Then I'll get going.
ثم سأذهب.
Take care.
يعتني.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I'm feeling a bit dizzy.
أشعر بالدوار قليلاً.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine, just...
أنا بخير ، فقط ...
I'm a little...
أنا قليلا ...
a little unsteady.
قليلا غير مستقر.
If you could...
إذا كنت تستطيع ...
give me a hand...
أعطني يد ...
that'd be great...
سيكون ذلك رائعًا ...
Did you drink just now?
هل شربت الآن؟
Why would a high schooler drink?
لماذا يشرب المدارس الثانوية؟
I thought it was juice.
اعتقدت أنه كان عصير.
So I just grabbed a cup. (official website: www.kisskh.la www.kisskh.co and www.kisskh.id other than this are fake)
لذلك أنا فقط أمسك كوب. (الموقع الرسمي: www.kisskh.la www.kisskh.co و www.kisskh.id بخلاف هذا مزيف)
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine. Just go.
أنا بخير. فقط اذهب.
Go on your way.
اذهب في طريقك.
Just go.
فقط اذهب.
Maybe sit down and sober up first?
ربما تجلس وترظة أولا؟
Sit here for a bit.
اجلس هنا قليلاً.
Rest here for a while, okay?
استرح هنا لفترة من الوقت ، حسنًا؟
Yeah, I'm good.
نعم ، أنا جيد.
No worries.
لا شكر على واجب.
My dad can't handle alcohol.
لا يستطيع والدي التعامل مع الكحول.
Maybe I've inherited that...
ربما ورثت ذلك ...
You sure you're fine?
أنت متأكد أنك بخير؟
Put some effort...
بذل بعض الجهد ...
Why are you so heavy?
لماذا أنت ثقيل جدا؟
One, two, three, go!
واحد ، اثنان ، ثلاثة ، اذهب!
Are you feeling better?
هل تشعر بتحسن؟
Yeah, I'm good.
نعم ، أنا جيد.
I'm still unsteady.
ما زلت غير مستقر.
Maybe put your shoulder under me?
ربما ضع كتفك تحتي؟
Isn't this the same?
أليس هذا هو نفسه؟
No, it's not stable.
لا ، إنه ليس مستقرًا.
This...
هذا...
this position is kind of uncomfortable.
هذا الموقف هو نوع من غير مريح.
Is this better?
هل هذا أفضل؟
Alright,
على ما يرام،
then just...
ثم فقط ...
Hold steady.
تمسك.
This is much better.
هذا أفضل بكثير.
Take your time, no rush.
خذ وقتك ، لا اندفاع.
I'm not in a hurry.
أنا لست في عجلة من أمري.
Does this work?
هل هذا يعمل؟
Is this comfortable?
هل هذا مريح؟
Yeah.
نعم.
[Straw Hat Hotpot]
[قش قبعة hotpot]
What's so funny?
ما هو مضحك جدا؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
You were definitely smiling.
كنت بالتأكيد تبتسم.
Wen Shuangjiang.
وين شوانغجيانغ.
I think I messed up.
أعتقد أنني عابث.
What?
ماذا؟
Tonight...
الليلة...
What I drank
ما شربت
was really juice.
كان حقا عصير.
No wonder you noticed.
لا عجب أنك لاحظت.
Noticed what?
لاحظت ماذا؟
I'm telling you...
أنا أخبرك ...
I'm not usually like this...
أنا لست مثل هذا عادة ...
And this time, what's your excuse?
وهذه المرة ، ما هو عذرك؟
Didn't you just say you could stand fine?
ألم تقل فقط أنك يمكن أن تقف على ما يرام؟
I can.
أنا استطيع.
Can you?
هل يمكنك؟
Wen Yifan.
وين ييفان.
What?
ماذا؟
Are you trying to chase me?
هل تحاول مطاردتي؟
If that's the case,
إذا كان هذا هو الحال ،
just be straightforward.
فقط كن واضحا.
Maybe...
ربما...
I'd consider it.
كنت أعتبر ذلك.
Not at the moment.
ليس في الوقت الحالي.
I'll let you know if I do.
سأخبرك إذا كنت أفعل.
Where are we going?
إلى أين نحن ذاهبون؟
Sit down.
اجلس.
Drunkard.
سكير.
Don't drink so much next time.
لا تشرب كثيرًا في المرة القادمة.
At your graduation,
في تخرجك ،
you drank over ten bottles.
لقد شربت أكثر من عشر زجاجات.
You're the real drunkard.
أنت السكر الحقيقي.
How do you know?
كيف علمت بذلك؟
Why did you drink so much?
لماذا شربت كثيرا؟
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
It's been so long.
لقد مر وقت طويل.
I don't even remember anymore.
لم أعد أتذكر بعد الآن.
Shuangjiang.
شوانغجيانغ.
Here.
هنا.
Drink this honey water.
اشرب ماء العسل هذا.
I don't want to, Dad.
لا أريد ذلك يا أبي.
Drink it.
اشربه.
Come on, be good.
تعال ، كن جيدًا.
Here.
هنا.
It'll warm you up.
سوف يسخنك.
Your hands and feet won't be cold.
لن تكون يديك وقدميك باردة.
Drink it, then go to sleep.
اشربه ، ثم اذهب للنوم.
Thank you, Sang Yan.
شكرا لك ، غنت يان.
If...
لو...
the renovation smell still lingers...
رائحة التجديد لا تزال باقية ...
you should stay here...
يجب أن تبقى هنا ...
for a little longer.
لفترة أطول قليلا.
Except for the two, legends of the Computer Science Department,
باستثناء الاثنين ، أساطير قسم علوم الكمبيوتر ،
Sang Yan and Duan Jiaxu.
سانج يان و دوان جياكو.
One didn't touch a drop,
لم يلمس المرء قطرة ،
the other downed bottles like water, over ten bottles.
الزجاجات الأخرى التي سقطت مثل المياه ، أكثر من عشر زجاجات.
Ten bottles?
عشر زجاجات؟
Who drank them?
من شربهم؟
Sang Yan.
غنى يان.
But that night,
لكن في تلك الليلة ،
he looked really off.
لقد نظر حقًا.
He was drinking alone,
كان يشرب بمفرده ،
barely saying a word.
بالكاد يقول كلمة.
He wouldn't listen to anyone.
لن يستمع إلى أي شخص.
Sang Yan,
غنى يان ،
was I really that bad to you?
هل كنت حقًا بهذا السوء بالنسبة لك؟
I'll treat you better from now on.
سأعاملك بشكل أفضل من الآن فصاعدًا.
Okay?
تمام؟
Sleepwalking again?
المشي نوم مرة أخرى؟
What triggers your sleepwalking?
ما الذي يؤدي إلى المشي في نومك؟
Even being drunk can trigger it?
حتى أن تكون في حالة سكر يمكن أن يؤدي ذلك؟
Just this once.
فقط هذا مرة واحدة.
Just one impulsive moment.
لحظة واحدة الاندفاع.
Aren't you taking advantage of me this time?
ألا تستفيد مني هذه المرة؟
Sang Yan,
غنى يان ،
I really hate
أنا حقا أكره
to meet you like this.
لمقابلتك مثل هذا.
I just wanted to do...
أردت فقط أن أفعل ...
what I really wanted to do back then.
ما أردت حقًا فعله في ذلك الوقت.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Let's get you home.
دعنا نأخذك إلى المنزل.
♪I couldn't keep my promise♪
♪ لم أستطع الحفاظ على وعدي ♪
♪My heart crossed the line again♪
♪ عبر قلبي الخط مرة أخرى ♪
♪Drawn closer by the countdown♪
♪ اقترب من العد التنازلي ♪
♪Until the fireworks fall♪
♪ حتى تسقط الألعاب النارية ♪
♪Should I hold back?♪
♪ هل يجب أن أتراجع؟ ♪
♪I'm not sure♪
♪ لست متأكدًا ♪
♪So I carefully, cautiously♪
♪ لذلك أنا بعناية ، بحذر ♪
♪Test the waters♪
♪ اختبار المياه ♪
♪Your every move plays in slow motion♪
♪ كل خطوة تلعب في حركة بطيئة ♪
♪Hesitant yet completely lost♪
♪ مترددة حتى الآن فقدت تماما ♪
♪I can't ignore the signs of falling for you♪
♪ لا يمكنني تجاهل علامات السقوط من أجلك ♪
♪No one else has ever moved me like this♪
♪ لم يحركني أي شخص آخر مثل هذا ♪
♪You're like the sun, shining bright♪
♪ أنت مثل الشمس ، ساطع مشرق ♪
♪Drawing me out of the chaos♪
♪ أخرجني من الفوضى ♪
♪Does your fire burns♪
♪ هل يحترق النار ♪
♪For me alone?♪
♪ بالنسبة لي وحدي؟ ♪
♪Even if the rain pours hard♪
♪ حتى لو كان المطر يصب بشدة ♪
♪Even if the world goes dark♪
♪ حتى لو أصبح العالم مظلمًا ♪
♪I'll stay right by your side♪
♪ سأبقى بجانبك ♪
♪Filling the emptiness with love♪
♪ ملء الفراغ بالحب ♪
♪No one else but you...♪
♪ لا أحد آخر لك ... ♪
That's all the time you get to hug me tonight?
هذا طوال الوقت الذي تعانقني الليلة؟
♪You are my one and only♪
♪ أنت واحد وفقط ♪
What did I just do?
ماذا فعلت للتو؟
Did I really pretend to sleepwalk?
هل تظاهرت حقًا بالنوم؟
Did I really take advantage of him?
هل استفدت منه حقًا؟
How could I hug him?
كيف يمكنني أن أعانقه؟
I was drunk.
كنت في حالة سكر.
Being drunk causes trouble.
أن تكون في حالة سكر يسبب المتاعب.
I'm never drinking again.
أنا لا أشرب مرة أخرى.
Even if I do, I won't act recklessly.
حتى لو فعلت ، لن أتصرف بتهور.
If I ever get the chance,
إذا حصلت على الفرصة ،
I want to apologize to Sang Yan
أريد أن أعتذر لغنغ يان
for what happened while I was drunk
لما حدث بينما كنت في حالة سكر
instead of carrying
بدلا من حمل
the blame
اللوم
for taking advantage of him.
للاستفادة منه.
I can't let this guilt weigh on me.
لا أستطيع ترك هذا الشعور بالذنب يثقل علي.
Sleep. Just sleep.
ينام. فقط النوم.
Everything will be fine tomorrow.
كل شيء سيكون على ما يرام غدا.
I made some porridge.
لقد صنعت بعض العصيدة.
Last night,
ليلة أمس،
I think I sleepwalked again.
أعتقد أنني نمت مرة أخرى.
I didn't do anything weird, right?
لم أفعل أي شيء غريب ، أليس كذلك؟
You did.
فعلت.
You just...
أنت فقط ...
hugged me for a moment.
عانقني للحظة.
You were pretty restrained.
كنت مقيدًا جدًا.
Sorry.
آسف.
How many times has this happened?
كم مرة حدث هذا؟
So,
لذا،
why are you feeling guilty now?
لماذا تشعر بالذنب الآن؟
I mean...
أعني...
Weren't you pretty cocky before?
ألم تكن مغرورًا جدًا من قبل؟
Every time we talked about this,
في كل مرة تحدثنا عن هذا ،
you always had excuses,
كان لديك دائمًا أعذار ،
blaming it on being unconscious.
إلقاء اللوم عليه على عدم الوعي.
I'd say one thing, you'd argue back.
أود أن أقول شيئًا واحدًا ، ستجادل مرة أخرى.
And in the end,
وفي النهاية ،
you even tried to pay me off.
حتى حاولت أن تدفع لي.
Wasn't that you?
أليس هذا أنت؟
How about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا ،
just keep yourself
فقط حافظ على نفسك
locked in your room at night.
مغلق في غرفتك في الليل.
Try not to come out.
حاول ألا تخرج.
Do we have a beast at home?
هل لدينا وحش في المنزل؟
Lock your door.
قفل بابك.
I can't exactly break in, can I?
لا أستطيع اقتحام بالضبط ، هل يمكنني ذلك؟
Your sleepwalking is pretty unique.
مكامن نومك فريد من نوعه.
It even involves taking advantage of people.
حتى أنه ينطوي على الاستفادة من الناس.
I never...
أنا أبدا ...
used to do that.
اعتاد أن تفعل ذلك.
I don't know why.
أنا لا أعرف لماذا.
So...
لذا...
it's just me you take advantage of?
أنا فقط أنت تستفيد منه؟
Or is this...
أم هذا ...
some new trick of flirting?
خدعة جديدة من المغازلة؟
I'm starting to doubt you now.
بدأت أشك فيك الآن.
Was it really sleepwalking?
هل كان حقا نوم المشي؟
Yes.
نعم.
Today,
اليوم،
you're awfully quiet.
أنت هادئ بفظاعة.
Am I?
انا
Whenever we talk about this,
كلما تحدثنا عن هذا ،
you usually have plenty of excuses.
عادة ما يكون لديك الكثير من الأعذار.
But it's happened so many times.
لكنه حدث عدة مرات.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
So now you just stay silent
حتى الآن أنت فقط تبقى صامتة
and accept your guilt?
وتقبل ذنبك؟
I'm full.
أنا ممتلئ.
Hey, beast.
مهلا ، الوحش.
What?
ماذا؟
Press the first floor.
اضغط على الطابق الأول.
I'm in a good mood today.
أنا في مزاج جيد اليوم.
I have a meeting near the TV station.
لدي اجتماع بالقرب من محطة التلفزيون.
I might as well give you a ride.
قد أعطيك أيضًا رحلة.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Not feeling well?
لا تشعر بخير؟
No.
لا.
Guess you burned all your energy sleepwalking.
أعتقد أنك أحرقت كل ما تبذلونه من طاقتك في النوم.
Last night when you lifted my shirt,
الليلة الماضية عندما رفعت قميصي ،
you were pretty enthusiastic.
كنت متحمسا جدا.
When did I lift your shirt?
متى رفعت قميصك؟
How do you know you didn't?
كيف تعرف أنك لم تفعل؟
Didn't you say
ألم تقل
that all I did...
أن كل ما فعلته ...
was hug you?
هل كان عناقك؟
Then maybe I got mixed up.
ثم ربما اختلطت.
It must've been last time.
يجب أن يكون آخر مرة.
It kept happening, after all.
ظل يحدث ، بعد كل شيء.
I can't remember them all.
لا أستطيع أن أتذكرهم جميعًا.
When I get time,
عندما أحصل على الوقت ،
I'll really go get checked at the hospital.
سأذهب حقًا في التحقق من المستشفى.
Sorry for the trouble.
آسف للمشكلة.
[Nanwu TV Station]
[محطة تلفزيون نانو]
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Be safe.
كن آمنًا.
Wen Yifan.
وين ييفان.
You've...
لديك ...
got something on your head.
حصلت على شيء على رأسك.
On my head?
على رأسي؟
Left side.
الجانب الأيسر.
Isn't this the left?
أليس هذا هو اليسار؟
Right side.
الجانب الأيمن.
Back right.
العودة اليمين.
You can't see it?
لا يمكنك رؤيته؟
Come closer.
اقترب.
Alright, done.
حسنا ، فعلت.
What was it?
ماذا كان؟
I have no idea.
ليس لدي أي فكرة.
Quit stalling. We're in a hurry.
ترك المماطلة. نحن في عجلة من أمرنا.
Stay safe.
ابق آمنًا.
Morning, Yifan.
صباح ، ييفان.
Morning.
صباح.
Yifan.
ييفان.
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
Are you dating...
هل تعود ...
Sang Yan?
غنت يان؟
No.
لا.
But he drove you to work
لكنه قادك إلى العمل
and even patted your head.
وحتى ربت رأسك.
So I thought...
لذلك فكرت ...
Alright, done.
حسنا ، فعلت.
Did that count as patting?
هل تم حساب ذلك على أنه باتن؟
Miss Wen!
ملكة جمال ون!
Miss Wen, you have a package.
ملكة جمال وين ، لديك حزمة.
Mine?
مِلكِي؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'll get it.
سأحصل عليه.
- Thanks. - No problem.
- شكرًا. - لا مشكلة.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Is it heavy?
هل هو ثقيل؟
Not really.
ليس حقيقيًا.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
No worries.
لا شكر على واجب.
Is it easy to carry?
هل من السهل حملها؟
Piece of cake.
قطعة من الكعكة.
Morning, Fang Li.
صباح ، فانغ لي.
- Morning! - Morning, Fang Li.
- صباح! - صباح ، فانغ لي.
Morning.
صباح.
Just leave it here.
فقط اتركه هنا.
Okay.
تمام.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Look.
ينظر.
What's up with those two?
ما الأمر مع هذين؟
I have no idea.
ليس لدي أي فكرة.
They always come and go together.
يأتون دائما ويذهبون معا.
Are they dating?
هل هم مواعدة؟
What are they talking about?
ما الذي يتحدثون عنه؟
Anyway, if you need help, I'm here.
على أي حال ، إذا كنت بحاجة إلى مساعدة ، فأنا هنا.
Whatever you need.
كل ما تحتاجه.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Want me to make you a coffee?
هل تريد مني أن أجعلك قهوة؟
No need, really.
لا حاجة ، حقا.
It's fine. I wanted one anyway.
لا بأس. أردت واحدة على أي حال.
Dian,
ديان ،
try using this next time you sleep.
حاول استخدام هذا في المرة القادمة التي تنام فيها.
It might stop the sleepwalking.
قد يوقف المشي.
Dian.
ديان.
I got the sleeping bag.
حصلت على حقيبة النوم.
Isn't the package way too big?
أليست طريقة الحزمة كبيرة جدًا؟
No need to thank me.
لا حاجة أن أشكرني.
I don't know if it'll work.
لا أعرف ما إذا كان سيعمل.
But give it a shot.
لكن أعطها رصاصة.
Alright, bye.
حسنا ، وداعا.
Okay.
تمام.
Yifan!
ييفان!
You're finally back!
لقد عدت أخيرًا!
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
So,
لذا،
Su Tian said
قال سو تيان
your roommate moved out.
انتقل زميلك في الغرفة.
I want
أريد
to move out of the dorms.
للخروج من المساكن.
So I was hoping to check out
لذلك كنت آمل أن أتحقق
the place you're renting.
المكان الذي تستأجره.
That might not be a good idea.
قد لا تكون هذه فكرة جيدة.
But I'm already here.
لكنني هنا بالفعل.
I know it's sudden,
أعلم أنه مفاجئ ،
but I promise
لكني أعدك
I won't take up much of your time.
لن أتناول الكثير من وقتك.
But...
لكن...
Coming home late without a word?
العودة إلى المنزل في وقت متأخر بدون كلمة؟
Why did you get off work so early today?
لماذا خرجت من العمل في وقت مبكر اليوم؟
Sorry for the intrusion, Senior Sang.
آسف للتسلل ، غنى كبار.
[Episode 12] [How to Be Happy? Staying with You]
[الحلقة 12] [كيف تكون سعيدا؟ البقاء معك]
[Nanwu TV Station]
[محطة تلفزيون نانو]
Thanks.
شكرًا.
[The story is not over yet...]
[القصة لم تنته بعد ...]
Wen Yifan.
وين ييفان.
You've... got something on your head.
لديك ... حصلت على شيء على رأسك.
You can't see it.
لا يمكنك رؤيته.
Come closer.
اقترب.
Alright, done.
حسنا ، فعلت.
Stay safe.
ابق آمنًا.
Morning, Yifan.
صباح ، ييفان.
Morning.
صباح.
♪Even the strongest heart♪
♪ حتى أقوى قلب ♪
♪Can waver♪
♪ يمكن أن يتردد ♪
♪And doubt its fire♪
♪ وشك في نيرانها ♪
♪But you never lost faith in me♪
♪ لكنك لم تفقد الإيمان بي أبدًا
♪In every battle, every dream I chased♪
♪ في كل معركة ، كل حلم طاردته ♪
♪There is meaning in every step I made♪
♪ هناك معنى في كل خطوة قمت بها ♪
♪Through the storm, through the endless night♪
♪ خلال العاصفة ، خلال الليل الذي لا نهاية له ♪
♪You were there, shining like a light♪
♪ كنت هناك ، مشرقة مثل الضوء ♪
♪Warm and bright♪
♪ دافئ ومشرق ♪
♪Standing right by my side♪
♪ يقف بجانبي يمينًا ♪
♪It was you, striding toward me through the storm♪
♪ كان أنت ، تخطت نحوي خلال العاصفة ♪
♪It was you, always cheering me on♪
♪ لقد كنت أنت ، دائماً تشجعني على ♪
♪The road is rough♪
♪ الطريق خشن ♪
♪The rain won't stop♪
♪ لن يتوقف المطر ♪
♪But with you here♪
♪ لكن معك هنا ♪
♪I fear no dark♪
♪ لا أخشى عدم الظلام ♪
♪Every thought, every memory is filled with you♪
♪ كل فكرة ، كل ذاكرة مليئة بك ♪
♪Marking our youth with every step we took♪
♪ وضع علامة على شبابنا مع كل خطوة اتخذناها ♪
♪When the downpour falls from the sky♪
♪ عندما يسقط هطول الأمطار من السماء ♪
♪You're the one holding out an umbrella for me♪
♪ أنت الشخص الذي يحمل مظلة بالنسبة لي ♪
♪When the white dove brings the news♪
♪ عندما تجلب الحمامة البيضاء الأخبار ♪
♪You're the first I want to tell♪
♪ أنت أول من أريد أن أقول ♪
♪I won't give up. I'll stay right here with you♪
♪ لن أستسلم. سأبقى هنا معك ♪
♪It was you, striding toward me through the storm♪
♪ كان أنت ، تخطت نحوي خلال العاصفة ♪
♪It was you, always cheering me on♪
♪ لقد كنت أنت ، دائماً تشجعني على ♪
♪The road is rough♪
♪ الطريق خشن ♪
♪The rain won't stop♪
♪ لن يتوقف المطر ♪
♪But with you here♪
♪ لكن معك هنا ♪
♪I will never give up♪
♪ لن أستسلم أبدًا ♪
♪You are my courage, my hope for the sky beyond♪
♪ أنت شجاعتي ، أملي في السماء وراء ♪
♪You are my light, shining through every night♪
♪ أنت نوري ، تشرق كل ليلة ♪
♪Even if I have to walk alone someday♪
♪ حتى لو اضطررت إلى المشي وحدي يومًا ما
♪I'll never truly be on my own♪
♪ لن أكون بمفردي حقًا
♪'Cause knowing you're here♪
♪ 'لأن معرفة أنك هنا ♪
♪I can brave the dark ahead♪
♪ يمكنني شجاعة الظلام إلى الأمام ♪
[Huge thanks to everyone involved and to all the fans of The First Frost!]
[شكر كبير لجميع المعنيين وجميع عشاق الصقيع الأول!]
[Treat yourself well, and the world will hold more love for you!]
[عامل نفسك جيدًا ، وسيحمل العالم المزيد من الحب لك!]